question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Science & Nature",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "History",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The two atomic bombs dropped on Japan by the United States in August 1945 were named &#039;Little Man&#039; and &#039;Fat Boy&#039;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "General Knowledge",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium", 
     "question": "The cover of The Beatles album &quot;Abbey Road&quot; featured a Volkswagen Beetle in the background.", 
     "correct_answer": "True", 
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }, 
    {"category": "General Knowledge", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium", 
     "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.", 
     "correct_answer": "False", 
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Science & Nature", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium", 
     "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.", 
     "correct_answer": "False", 
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Science: Computers", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium", 
     "question": "The very first recorded computer &quot;bug&quot; was a moth found inside a Harvard Mark II computer.", 
     "correct_answer": "True", 
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Science & Nature", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium", 
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.", 
     "correct_answer": "True", 
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium", 
     "question": "There aren&#039;t any live-action clones in &quot;Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith&quot;.", 
     "correct_answer": "True", 
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Science & Nature", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium", 
     "question": "Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.", 
     "correct_answer": "True", 
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Sports", 
     "type": "boolean", 
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Soccer player Cristiano Ronaldo opened a museum dedicated to himself.", 
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }, 
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Japanese Shinkansen beat the French TGV&#039;s speed record for fastest electric rail train.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;I disapprove of what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it&quot; is a quote from French philosopher Voltaire.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The animated film &quot;Spirited Away&quot; won the Academy Award for Best Animated Feature at the 75th Academy Awards in 2003.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; takes place on Shadow Moses Island.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "MacOS is based on Linux.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "AMD created the first consumer 64-bit processor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In 1967, a magazine published a story about extracting hallucinogenic chemicals from bananas to raise moral questions about banning drugs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {
        "category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The average lifespan of a wildcat is only around 5-6 years. ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The capital of the US State Ohio is the city of Chillicothe.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "United States President Ronald Reagan was the first president to appoint a woman to the Supreme Court. ", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "For his performance at ComplexCon 2016 in Long Beach, California, Skrillex revived his &quot;Mothership&quot; set piece for one night only.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "E = MC3", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Pistons were added to Minecraft in Beta 1.5.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Joan Cusack starred in the 2009 disaster movie, &quot;2012&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Adolf Hitler was accepted into the Vienna Academy of Fine Arts.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In the video game &quot;Transistor&quot;, &quot;Red&quot; is the name of the main character.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Wilt Chamberlain scored his infamous 100-point-game against the New York Knicks in 1962.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The movie &quot;Tron&quot; received an Oscar nomination for Best Visual Effects.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Sound can travel through a vacuum.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Donald Duck played the role of Bob Cratchit in Disney&#039;s 1983 adaptation of A Christmas Carol.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The title of the 1969 film &quot;Krakatoa, East_of Java&quot; is incorrect, as Krakatoa is in fact west of Java.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Sir Issac Newton served as a Member of Parliament, but the only recorded time he spoke was to complain about a draft in the chambers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In 2008, Usain Bolt set the world record for the 100 meters with one shoelace untied.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "ATP tennis hosted several tournaments on carpet court before being replaced to reduce injuries.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;Neutral Milk Hotel&quot; is a real band.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]  # Compare this snippet from data.p
